const STORE = [
    {
      question: 'How many species of giraffe are there?',
      answers: [
        'One',
        'Five',
        'Twelve',
        'Ten'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'One'
    },
    {
    question: 'Where do giraffes live?',
    answers: [
      'South America',
        'Africa',
        'Asia',
        'Alaska'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Africa'
    },
    {
      question: 'What kind of terrain do giraffes prefer?',
      answers: [
        'Rocky slopes',
          'Dense forests',
          'Freshwater marshes',
          'Open grassy plains'
        ],
        correctAnswer:'Open grassy plains'
    },
    {
      question: 'To what height do male giraffes grow?',
      answers: [
        '15 feet(4.6 m)',
          '21 feet(6.4 m)',
          '18 feet(5.5 m)',
          '13 feet(3.9 m)'
         ],
         correctAnswer: '18 feet(5.5 m)'
    },
    {
      question: 'To what height do female giraffes grow?',
      answers: [
        '15 feet (4.6 m)',
          '18 feet (5.5 m)',
          '12 feet (3.7 m)',
          '10 feet (3.0 m)'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '15 feet (4.6 m)'
    },
    {
      question: 'How long is the giraffeâ€™s neck?',
      answers: [
       'Seven feet (2.1 m)',
         'Six feet (1.8 m)',
       'Nine feet (2.7 m)',
         'Eight feet (2.4 m)'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Seven feet (2.1 m)'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the giraffes has horns?',
      answers: [
        'Only Masai male giraffes',
          'Neither sex',
          'Certain types of adult Transvaal giraffe',
          'Both sexes'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Both sexes'
    },
    {
      question: 'With such a long neck and long legs, how does the giraffe drink water?',
      answers: [
        'Neck is long enough',
        'Spreads its front legs',
          'Kneels',
        'Giraffes do not drink water'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Spreads its front legs'
    },
    {
      question: 'At what speed can giraffes run?',
      answers: [
        '24 miles per hour (38 km/h)',
          '29 miles per hour (47 km/h)',
          '35 miles per hour (56 km/h)',
          '32 miles per hour (51 km/h)'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '29 miles per hour (47 km/h)'
    },
    {
      question: 'What are the social habits of giraffes?',
      answers: [
        'They live in herds',
          'They only group together when danger is present',
          'They live in pairs',
          'Except for mating season they are usually alone'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'They live in herds'
    },
    ];